Fear finds new depths.
Something in the Water is a thriller, horror film
directed by Hayley Easton Street.
After lesbian couple Meg and Kayla split following a traumatic homophobic incident, their three
friends are intent on mending the rift during the wedding of Lizzie at a paradise resort.
But a pre-wedding boat excursion turns to disaster and the
wedding breakfast is likely to be the five girls!
Meg, played by Hiftu Quasem.
Kayla, played by Natalie Mitson.
Lizzie, played by Lauren Lyle.
Cam, played by Nicole Rieko Setsuko.
Ruth, played by Ellouise Shakespeare-Hart.
Dominic, played by Gabriel Prevost.
Something in the Water is a 2024 British survival thriller film
directed by Hayley Easton Street and written by Cat Clarke.
Its plot follows a group of friends who meet up for a wedding in the
Caribbean, and become stranded in the sea after their hire boat sinks.
The film explores themes of shark attack, female
friendship, survival, wedding, shark.
The tone is dark and intense.